Randa Airsheed Ainoor
randaalrsheed4@gmail.com 01142994009  Maadi,Cairo
Summary:
I have 2 years of experience in social developing with Community schools international foundation on both operational and field implementation roles; I hold <b>Aviation and Tecnology</b> diploma with focus on <b>Cabin Crew</b> . In addition to extensive online studies on self-development, functional and social studies.
- Two years of experience in the leading group, experience in management, and two years' experience as interprator .
Professional experience
Teaching experience from (2015-2017)
This is a watermark for trial version, register to get full one!  - Coordinating with students' families to ensure receiving their fees receipt .  VIPBenefits: - Data Enter and IT teacher - Writing Report - Prepare monthly school activities.
-I worked as English teacher for El-Etihad School in Sudan.  1. Converts the whole document.  Work Experience  2. No trial watermark on the output documents.
K2 Resturant supervisor From (2016 – 2017)  -Follow up with the staff to ensure everything is done as planned.  Remove it Now
- Trainer for new comers.
- HR assistant in a hotel.
-writing monthly reports.

Volunteering Experience\_\_\_\_\_

- -Community mentor Care From (May 2020 October2018).
- Community peer Aducator at Care Organization.
- -Community Outreach- Tadamon Community Center.
- Contribute in distributing foot boxes, winter closes and blankets .

- Provide awareness workshops for refugees in Maadi during Covid-19.
Education
- Diploma of Aviation and Technology March 2013 – July2015.
-Sudanese High School -2012
Courses
- Excel to MySQL: Analytic
Techniques for Business

- IBM Professional Certificate in data analysic
- | English Language —Biritsh Institute;

- ICDL - Coursea

## This is a watermark for trial version, register to get full one! - First aid workshop- Sudanese Red Crescent Society

## VIPBenefits:

- 1. Converts the whole document.
- 2. No trial watermark on the output documents.

Remove it Now